He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
Genta, Mitsuhiko, Ayumi, and I were playing Kick-the-Can,
كنتُ ألعب لعبة "ركل العلبة" مع غينتا وميتسوهيكو وأيومي
but soon found ourselves having lunch at a restaurant
وقادتنا الظروف لتناول الغداء في مطعم
with Two-Mix vocalist, Takayama Minami-san.
رفقة مُغنّية فرقة تو-ميكس، تاكاياما مينامي-سان
She had snuck out to look for her missing partner, Nagano Shiina-san.
كانت قد تسلّلت خارج قاعة الحفل بحثاً عن زميلها ناغانو شينا-سان الذي لم يجب على اتّصالاتها
But at the restaurant, she was kidnapped before our very eyes!
!لكن عند المطعم، اُختطفت تاكاياما-سان أمام أعيننا
The kidnappers demanded the bag she left at the restaurant.
كان طلب الخاطفين هي الحقيبة التي تركتها في المطعم
What's more, they demanded that we take it.
فوق ذلك، طلبوا أن نكون نحن من يجلبها
It appeared they were after a Two-Mix demo tape.
يبدو أنّ هدفهم كان الشريط الاستعراضيّ لـ تو-ميكس
After taking the bag as ordered, the kidnappers contacted us
بعد أخذنا الحقيبة كما أمروا، اتّصل المختطِفون بنا
and said to lose the officers and have Ayumi deliver the tape alone.
وأخبرونا أن نضلل رجال الشرطة الذين كانوا يتبعوننا ونترك أيومي تسلّم الشريط الاستعراضي بمفردها
I can't put Ayumi in danger!
لا يمكنني تعريض أيومي للخطر
So, I devised a plan...
...لذا فكّرتُ بخطّة
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Good work, little girl.
أحسنتِ يا صغيرتي
There aren't any cops around, I hope?
لا يوجد أيّ رجال شرطة في الجوار، صحيح؟
No, there doesn't seem to be anyone...
كلا، لا يبدو أنّ هناك أحد
Perfect.
حسنٌ، ممتاز
Ready to come, like I told ya?
مستعدّة للقدوم الآن كما أخبرتك؟
Yeah...
نعم
I'll try my hardest!
!سأبذل جهدي
"The Popular Artists Abduction Case (Part 2)."
الجزء الثاني
What?! Conan-kun and Ayumi-kun switched places?!
!ماذا؟! بادل كونان-كن وأيومي-كن مكانيهما؟
My word...
...يا للهول
The kidnappers are after the demo tape!
!كان هدف المختطفين هو الشريط الاستعراضيّ
They said to have Ayumi deliver it and to lose the police--
...طلبوا أن نجعل أيومي تسلّمه ونضلّل الشرطة
...so Conan-kun switched with me!
!فبادلني كونان-كن
But, why didn't you tell us you switched?
لكن لمَ لم تخبرونا أنّكما تبادلتما؟
They'd be most off guard if we let them think their plan worked!
سيخففون حذرهم إذا جعلناهم يعتقدون أنّ الخطّة نجحت
So, Conan-kun said we couldn't let anyone know until then!
لذا أخبرنا كونان-كن بألّا نبوح لأحد !حتّى يتمّ ذلك
But, now we can't locate the kidnappers...
...لكن لا يمكننا تحديد مكان المختطفين الآن
Conan-kun is in danger.
كونان-كن في خطر
Oh, he said that these Tracking Glasses should--
بخصوص ذلك، قال أنّه إذا استعملنا ...نظّارات التعقّب هذه
At this rate, Conan's gonna get all the credit!
سينال كونان المجد كلّه لوحده على هذا النحو
We can still find their hideout and then tell the police!
!يمكننا إيجاد مخبئهم ثمّ إخبار الشرطة
And then, after we've saved Two-Mix...
...بعدها، عندما ننقذ تو-ميكس
Junior Detective League Saves the Day!!
إنجاز كبير لفرقة !!فتيان التحرّي
Thank you, boys!
!شكراً لكم يا أولاد
It's all thanks to you!
!كلّ هذا بفضلكم
Ok! Let's go catch those kidnappers!
!حسنٌ، لنعتقل نحن فرقة فتيان التحرّي الخاطفين
What are you shouting about?
لمَ تصرخون؟
No, we were saying, "Oh! We're so hungry!"
...لا، كنّا نقول
Right?
صحيح؟
Y-Yeah... We were saying, "Oh! We're so hungry!"
"!أ-أجل! كنّا نقول "كم نشعر بالجوع
Well, we're off to buy some food!
إذاً، سنذهب لشراء طعام
Come back quickly, now.
ارجعوا سريعاً
We will!
!حاضر
♪ We're so hungry! We're so hungry! We're so hungry! ♪
!كم نشعر بالجوع! كم نشعر بالجوع
Hello?
مرحباً؟
As agreed, it looks like you came alone.
يبدو أنّك أتيتِ بمفردك وفقما اتّفقنا يا صغيرتي
Now, bring the tape up to the 2nd floor of the nearby warehouse.
هيّا، اجلبي الشريط للطابق الثاني في المستودع المجاور لك
Your beloved Two-Mix is waiting!
فرقة تو-ميكس التي تحبّينها بانتظارك
Won't be needing you anymore!
انتهى دوركما الآن
Say your prayers while you still have time.
فلتتلوا آخر دعواتكما قبل نفاد الوقت
I brought it, Mister!
!أحضرتُه يا سيّدي
Oh, thanks, little girl!
!هكذا إذاً، شكراً لك يا صغيرتي
Who're you--
...لمَ أنت
Huh? Where's the guy from the coffee shop?
ماذا؟ الرجل الذي كان في المقهى ليس موجوداً؟
Is he out somewhere?
أخرج لمكانٍ ما؟
That the place?
أذاك هو المكان؟
No question about it!
لا شكّ في الأمر
Do you think Conan-kun is ok?
أتظنّان كونان-كن بخير؟
Now what?
ماذا سنفعل الآن؟
We need to contact the police for now.
علينا الاتّصال بالشرطة مبدئياً
There's a phone booth over there!
توجد حجرة هاتف هناك
Ok! Let's go!
!حسنٌ، لنذهب
Yeah!
!أجل
1-1-9...
...واحد واحد تسعة
Wait! That's the fire department! The police is 110!
!انتظر! هذا مركز الإطفاء يا غينتا-كن رقم الشرطة 110
Oh yeah.
...صحيح
And don't you need to press this button?
أيضاً أليس عليك ضغط هذا الزرّ؟
Oh yeah.
أجل
This is 110.
نعم، هنا 110
Hello? Where'd you go, little boy? Hello?
مرحباً؟ ما الخطب يا فتى؟
Hello?!
!مرحباً؟
Ow!
!مؤلم
How did you find us?!
كـ-كيف وجدتنا؟
I was told to bring this tape here.
أخبروني بأن أجلب هذا الشريط هنا
Yeah, they really questioned us about where the tape was...
...صحيح، استجوبونا بشدّة عن مكان الشريط
But why would they want it?
لكن لمَ قد يريدانه؟
Let's save the details for after we've escaped.
لنترك التفاصيل إلى ما بعد هروبنا من هنا
And the police are on their way.
والشرطة ستأتي قريباً
The police?!
الشرطة؟
They're on their way here right now, using my Tracking Glasses.
إنّهم في طريقهم الآن باستعمال نظّارات التعقّب خاصتي
It homes in on this badge's transmitter.
يقودهم جهاز الإرسال على هذه الشارة
Who are you?
مـ-من أنت؟
Edogawa Conan.
إيدوغاوا كونان
A detective.
مُتحرٍّ
Detective?!
-مـ
Let's hurry before the other kidnapper comes back...
لنسرع قبل أن يرجع المُختطف الآخر
Are those your "Tracking Glasses"?
...أنظّارات التعقّب التي تقصدها
Conan-kun...
...كونان-كن
You guys!
!أنتم؟
What're you doing here?!
!لمَ أنتم هنا؟
I caught 'em snooping around here.
أمسكتُ بهم وهم يتجسّسون خارجاً
You idiots! Why didn't you give the glasses to the police?!
!حمقى! لمَ لم تعطوا النظّارات للشرطة؟
We just wanted...
...أردنا
You'll have plenty of time to fight...
...سيكون لديكم وقت كثير للشجار
...in the afterlife!
!في العالم الآخر
So long.
وداعاً
I'm nice enough to turn you into ashes. Be grateful.
سأحوّلكم لرماد معاً، فلتكونوا مُمتنين
Wait! At least tell us why you kidnapped us!
!انتظر! أخبرنا بسبب اختطافك لنا على الأقل
Ask Buddha in the afterlife.
اسألي الإله في العالم الآخر
"The countdown bell sounds..."
"يتردد قرع جرس العدّ التنازليّ"
"and says to change hearts and run."
"ويخبرك بأن تغيّر قلبك وتركض"
"It rings once, twice..."
"ها هو يتردد مرّة، اثنتين"
"Like the sound of off-season fireworks..."
"كصوت ألعاب نارية خارج موسمها"
"Like the sound of someone, somewhere, confessing their love..."
"صوت إفصاح أحدهم عن حبّه في مكان ما"
You damn kid...
...أيّها الصبيّ
That's right. The lyrics on the Two-Mix demo tape.
أجل، هذه كلمات الأغنية على الشريط الاستعراضيّ لـ تو-ميكس
And the reason you kidnapped Two-Mix!
!وسبب اختطافك لهما
Isn't that right, Miyahara Satoshi-san?
ألستُ محقّاً يا مياهارا ساتوشي-سان؟
The night of New Year's Eve, you killed a man near Shoenji Temple
في ليلة رأس السنة، قتلتَ رجلاً مجهولاً قرب معبد شوينجي
and were investigated by Inspector Megure.
وحقّق معك المفتّش ميغوري
New Year's Eve?!
ليلة رأس السنة؟
Shoenji?
شوينجي؟
That's where we came up with that song!
!هناك خطرت لنا الأغنية
There was a murder near that temple when the bell rang at 11:50...
وقعت بالقرب جريمة قتل عند قرابة ...الحادية عشرة وخمسون دقيقة
Since the man died holding the gun, had gunpowder on his hands,
عندما وصلت الشرطة، وجدت آثار بارود على يد الرجل الميت المُمسك بالمسدّس
and there was an empty shell in the barrel,
وكان هناك عيار فارغ في حجرة الإطلاق
the police believed your claim that it went off during your struggle
فصدّقت الشرطة مقولتك بأنّ رجلاً متنكّراً هاجمك بمسدّس وانطلقت رصاصة أثناء الاشتباك
with the gun-toting maniac.
فاعتُبرت الحادثة دفاعاً عن النفس
But, that wasn't actually the case.
لكن لم يكن ذلك الواقع
You had brought the gun to kill him from the very start!
كنتَ قد جلبت المسدّس معك بنيّة قتل ذاك الرجل من البداية
After shooting him through the heart with the first shot,
،بعد إطلاق الرصاصة الأولى في قلبه
you loaded another bullet into the barrel and fired at the ground...
لقمّت المسدّس برصاصة أخرى وأطلقت على الأرض
...with his hand on the gun, to leave behind traces of gunpowder!
والمسدّس بيد الضحيّة كي تنتقل آثار البارود له
There were no witnesses around, so while you called the police,
لم يكن هناك شهود في الجوار، لذا بينما اتّصلت بالشرطة
the man sleeping outside was to run off with the extra bullet and shell
تخلّص الرجل الآخر النائم خارجاً من الرصاصة الأخرى والعيار
to put you in the clear.
فتكتمل روايتك
But, there were people who heard those sounds...
...لكن كان هناك أشخاص قد سمعوا تلك الأصوات
You don't mean--
...أ-أتقصد
Yeah. You two from Two-Mix.
أجل، أنتما ثنائيّ تو-ميكس
The "countdown bell" was the New Year's bell.
جرس العدّ التنازلي" يرمز لجرس رأس السنة"
The two fireworks were the two gunshots.
والصوتان المترددان كالألعاب النارية كانا صوتي الطلقتين
And the line, "1996 just flew right by," indicated the year it happened.
"ومقدّمة الأغنية التي تقول "مرّت 1996 بلمح البصر تشير لعام وقوع الحادثة
Add in Shoenji Temple, which you mentioned on the radio,
أضف ذلك لمعبد شوينجي الذي ذُكر في بثّ تو-ميكس
and the time and place of the gunshots becomes clear.
وستعرف زمن ومكان الطلقتين الناريتين
I assume you heard the radio show the demo tape was played on.
استمعتَ للبثّ الذي أذاع الشريط الاستعراضيّ، أليس كذلك؟
So you kidnapped Two-Mix...
لذا اختطفت تو-ميكس
...to get rid of the tape and them before the police found out!
للتخلّص من الشريط قبل أن !تنتبه الشرطة لذلك
Pretty clever.
يا لدهائك
That's right. I'm Miyahara Satoshi.
معك حقّ، أنا مياهارا ساتوشي
The guy I killed was an old bank-robbing partner of ours.
الرجل الذي قتلتُه كان شريكاً في عمليّة سطو سابقة
He suddenly threatened to tell the cops, so I offed him.
أتى وبدأ بتهديدي بإخبار الشرطة فجأةً، فتخلّصتُ منه
Couldn't you have just run off after that?
ألم يكن بإمكانك الهرب بعد ذلك وحسب؟
I had no choice.
لم يكن لديّ خيار
A temple priest had seen my face while I was on my way there.
فقد رأى أحد رهبان المعبد وجهي وأنا في طريقي للقائه
Luckily, he was hard of hearing.
كان ضعيف السمع لحسن الحظّ
Said he had to stay at the temple to ring the bell, so I let him live.
قال أنّه سيبقى في المعبد بمفرده ليقرع الأجراس، فتركتُه يعيش
Never expected someone to hear the shots and make a song about it...
لكن لم يخطر لي أبداً أنّ هنالك من سمع الطلقات وألّف أغنيةً بها
A cell phone, huh? Give it here!
ماذا؟ هاتف خلويّ؟
This is that long-haired guy's phone I had my partner hold onto...
هذا هاتف الشاب طويل الشعر هنا الذي جعلتُ شريكي يحتفظ به
Damn, can't be careless around you...
يا إلهي، صبي يتصيّد الإهمال
But, even if you did call the police, you'd die before they get here...
لكن حتّى لو استدعيت الشرطة، ستحترقون قبل أن يصلوا هنا غالباً
Well then, please enjoy your stay.
فلتستمتعوا بوقتكم المتبقّي يا سادة
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Oh, Inspector Megure. I let them and those kids go unharmed.
مفتّش ميغوري؟ أطلقتُ سراح الاثنين والأطفال بلا أيّ إصابات
Bye.
وداعاً
That's odd. He didn't even mention Conan-kun switching places...
غريب، لم يقل شيئاً عن تبدّل كونان-كن وأيومي
Inspector. I just got word on the radio
حضرة المفتّش، وصلنا بلاغ على المذياع
that some kids had called 110 and asked for you.
بأنّ طفلاً اتّصل بـ 110 وطلب الكلام معك
What?! When?!
!ماذا؟ متى؟
Um, some fifteen minutes ago.
...حسناً، قبل 15 دقيقة تقريباً
Why didn't they tell us sooner?!
!لمَ لم يخبرونا قبلاً؟
Do we know the location?!
!أتعرفون الموقع؟
No, it was too short to trace...
كلا، كانت قصيرة فلم يستطيعوا تعقّبها
This is bad! If the kidnappers were the ones who hung up...
يا للهول! لو كان المختطف هو ...من اكتشف الاتّصال وقطع الخط
It's no use! It's not budging!
!لا جدوى! لا يتزحزح البتّة
Ok! Time for my Power Kick Shoes...
...حسنٌ، سأستعمل حذاء مضاعفة قوّة الركل
Move!
!ابتعد
Ow! It's no use!
!تبّاً! لا جدوى
Are you kids ok?!
أأنتم بخير يا صغار؟
This is bad! At this rate, we won't survive!
!هذا سيّئ! لن ينجو أحد على هذا النحو
Hey! Don't breathe the smoke! Get lower to the--
...إيّاكم أن تستنشقوا الدخان! انخفضوا و
Little boy!
!يا فتى
Are you ok?!
أأنت بخير يا فتى؟
Pull yourself together!
!تماسك
Little boy!
!يا فتى
Talk about a nuisance...
يا للحِمل
Those annoying cops...
...الشرطة المزعجة
Hey! Quit--
...أنتم! يكفي
Yay! We're long gone!
!مرحى! هربنا منذ فترة
What?!
!ماذا؟
We're calling from a police box!
!نحن نتّصل من مركز الشرطة
See for yourself if you don't believe me!
اذهب وانظر بنفسك إذا !كنت لا تصدّقنا
That's impossible!
!مـ-مستحيل
They're gone!
!اختفوا
How did...
...كـ-كيف
How did they get out?
كيف خرجوا؟
We did it!
!نجحنا
See! Told you this Earring Cell Phone was useful!
!رأيتِ؟ كان هاتف القرط الخلويّ هذا مفيداً
It sure was!
!بالفعل
Hurry! We can still get to the concert in time!
لنسرع! لا يزال بإمكاننا الوصول !للقاعة قبل الحفلة
Everyone duck!
!انخفضوا جميعاً
Shiina-kun!
!شينا-كن
Don't mock me, kids!
!لا تستخفّوا بي يا صغار
I'm gonna kill each one of you!
!سأقتلكم فرداً فرداً
Bastard!
!الوغد
That was awesome, Minami-chan!
!مذهل يا مينامي-تشان
Talk about strong!
!يا لقوّتها
That was close...
فعلتُها في آخر لحظة
Ten minutes later, a fire truck arrived with police cars,
بعد 10 دقائق، وصلت عربة إطفاء مع مجموعة من سيّارات الشرطة
and the two-man gang was put under arrest.
واعتقلت الشرطة المجرمين
Naturally, the Junior Detective League got a harsh scolding,
تلقّت فرقة فتيان التحرّي توبيخاً شديداً بالطبع
but Takayama Minami-san stuck up for us, so we were acquitted
،لكنّ تاكاياما مينامي-سان تدخّلت وأُصفح عنّا للوقت الراهن
and then we rushed to the Budokan in Inspector Megure's car.
ثمّ أسرعنا لقاعة بودوكان بسيّارة المفتّش ميغوري
What are you guys doing?!
!ما الذي تفعلونه؟
It's already thirty minutes past!
!تأخّرتم 30 دقيقة بالفعل
Not good. The crowd's getting antsy.
هذا سيّئ، الحضور يتذمرون
We need to go change, so wait backstage.
علينا تغيير ثيابنا، لذا انتظروا في كواليس المسرح
Backstage?
كواليس المسرح؟
We wanna introduce you to everyone later!
سنقدّمكم للجميع لاحقاً
Everyone?
للـ-للجميع؟
Hey! Is Minami-chan still not here?
لم تأت مينامي-تشان بعد؟
Geez! What's she doing?!
يا إلهي! ما الذي تفعله؟
Um... Is this backstage?
المعذرة... أهذه كواليس المسرح؟
Hey, now! You're not allowed back here!
!أنتم! ليس مسموحاً لكم الدخول هنا
Get back to your seats!
!ارجعوا لمقاعدكم
Takayama-san told us to come here...
أخبرتنا تاكاياما-سان أن نأتي هنا
Eh?! Minami-chan's here?!
!ماذا؟ وصلت مينامي-تشان؟
Ok! Put the opening song on standby!
!حسنٌ! ضعوا الأغنية الافتتاحية في وضعية الاستعداد
Hey! Someone go to the dressing rooms and ask how much longer!
أنتم! ليذهب أحدكم لغرفة تبديل الملابس !ويسألها كم ستستغرق أكثر
Right!
!حاضر
Say, what does this do?
المعذرة، ما الذي يفعله هذا؟
Hey! Don't touch that!
!انتبه! لا تلمسه
Sorry!
!حاضر
Whoops!
!انطفأت الأنوار
My turn!
!حسنٌ، دوري
Hey!
!أنت
Oh no! The song's started!
!مـ-مشكلة! بدأت الأغنية
What do we do?! They're not here yet!
!ما العمل؟ لم يأتيا بعد
Stop the song!
!أوقفوا الأغنية بسرعة
Are you crazy?! They'd get even madder if we did that!
أحمق! إذا فعلنا ذلك سيغضبون !أكثر من ذي قبل
So what do we do?!
!ماذا نفعل إذاً؟
I'm figuring that out!
!أفكّر بذلك الآن
Say, do you have this song's lyrics?
أخبروني، ألديكم كلمات هذه الأغنية؟
Eh? Yeah, they're in that CD case...
ماذا؟ إنّها موجودة في علبة ...ذاك القرص الرقمي
But, what do you want them for...
لكن لمَ تريدها؟
Hey, you're not gonna...
...ا-انتظر، أيمكن
♪ Break my lies ♪
♪ حطّم أكاذيبي ♪
♪ Chase after me again as I rush off ♪
♪ الحق بي مجدداً ♪
♪ Save my heart ♪
♪ أنقذ قلبي ♪
♪ I'm actually waiting... Embrace me... ♪
♪ أنا أنتظر في الواقع... عناقك لي ♪
♪ Now return to love ♪
♪ لنرجع للحُب الآن ♪
I could swear I've heard that singing voice before...
...أشعر أنّي سمعتُ هذا الغناء قبلاً
Don't joke like that!
دعيك من المزح المخيفة
Who the hell's singing?!
!من الذي يغنّي؟
Talk about tone-deaf...
إحساسه الموسيقيّ معدوم
But it is Takayama-san's voice...
...لكن هذا صوت تاكاياما-سان
Bad idea?
أكان سيّئاً؟
♪ It hurt that I couldn't say that one little thing ♪
لأنّي لم أستطع البوح بتلك ♪ ♪ الكلمة بصراحة، قد آذيتك
♪ as I sought this warm hand almost in tears ♪
تسعى يدي لدفئك بشدّة ♪ ♪ بحيث تكاد دموعي تسيل
Look!
...أليس ذاك
Conan-kun...
!كونان-كن
♪ Even so, I searched because I still believed deep down ♪
مع ذلك، بحثت لأنّني ♪ ♪ ما زلتُ أؤمن في أعماقي
♪ Break my lies ♪
♪ حطّم أكاذيبي ♪
♪ Realize the quivering truth in my eyes ♪
♪ فلتلاحظ هذه الحقيقة المتموّجة في عيني ♪
♪ Save my heart ♪
♪ أنقذ قلبي ♪
♪ Kiss these trembling lips ♪
♪ فلتقبّل هاتين الشفتين المرتجفتين ♪
♪ Now return to love ♪
♪ ونرجع للحُب الآن ♪
♪ What I felt when I was with you wasn't weakness ♪
ما شعرتُ به عندما كنت معك ♪ ♪ لم يكن ضعفاً
♪ it was a kind of serenity that made up for something I lacked ♪
بل طمأنينةً عوّضت عن ♪ ♪ فجوةً داخلي
♪ The more important the person, the more afraid I am to lose them ♪
كلما كان المرء عزيزاً عليك، خشيت ♪ ♪ فقدانك له
♪ All alone in the crowd, I searched for a place to return to ♪
♪ وحيداً في الحشود، بحثتُ عن مكان أرجع له ♪
♪ Break my lies ♪
♪ حطّم أكاذيبي ♪
♪ Snatch away the pain-- ♪
انتزع الألم الذي لا أستطيع ♪ ♪ التعبير عنه بكلمات
And so the Two-Mix concert that we barged into ended without a hitch.
وهكذا، أُقيمت حفلة تو-ميكس في بودوكان التي شاركنا فيها نحن فرقة فتيان التحرّي
♪ Now return to love ♪
♪ فلنرجع للحُب الآن ♪
See ya later!
نراكما لاحقاً إذاً
Good work today!
!عمل مُوفق
Good work!
عمل مُوفق
So, what did you think of singing on stage?
إذاً، كيف كان الغناء على المسرح؟
It was the greatest!
!رائعاً جدّاً
I was moved!
!تأثّرتُ كثيراً
I could do it again!
!أريد فعلها مجدداً
I bet! Just once, and you're hooked!
أليس كذلك؟ تختبر الأمر مرّةً وتصبح متعلّقاً
So, what did the little detective think?
وماذا عنك؟ ما رأي المتحرّي الصغير؟
How was the concert?
أسألك عن رأيك في الحفلة
Come on in.
تفضّل
So, this is your dressing room?
غرفة تبديل تو-ميكس؟
Oh, Inspector! Can we help you?
حضرة المفتّش! أيمكننا مساعدتك؟
I'm sorry to ask when you're so exhausted,
،أعتذر على طلب هذا رغم إرهاقكما
but I was hoping you could come to the station to give a statement...
لكنّي كنت آمل أن تستطيعا مرافقتنا للمركز للإدلاء بإفادتيكما
Oh, okay. Just a minute.
هكذا إذاً؟ انتظر قليلاً من فضلك
Please, take your time...
المعذرة، خذي وقتك
That was a wonderful concert!
كانت تلك حفلةً مذهلة بحقّ
Thank you.
شكراً جزيلاً
Here you go!
هاكم
This is for saving us today! Practice at home, ok?
!هذه هديّتكم لإنقاذنا اليوم تمرّنوا في البيت، اتّفقنا؟
Ok!
!حاضر
And some for you, too!
واثنتان لكما سيّدي المفتّش
Why, thank you!
!نحن مُمتنان
Could I get autographs and pictures, too?
أيمكنني الحصول على صورة وتوقيع أيضاً؟
Sure!
!بالطبع
Ready?! What's 1 plus 1?
!مستعدّون؟ ما 1 زائد 1؟
Two!
!اثنان
Karaoke Box
صندوق الكاراوكي
♪ Break my lies ♪
♪ حطّم أكاذيبي ♪
♪ Chase after me again as I rush off ♪
♪ الحق بي مجدّداً ♪
That's all he's been singing...
...هذا كلّ ما كان يغنّيه
But he hasn't gotten any better...
لكنّه لم يتحسّن البتّة
♪ I'm actually waiting... Embrace me... ♪
♪ أنا أنتظر في الواقع... عناقك لي ♪
♪ Now return to love ♪
♪ فلنرجع للحُب الآن ♪
♪ Return to love ♪
♪ فلنرجع للحُب ♪
The old man was staying at the hospital, but just when he woke up,
،كان العمّ نائماً في المشفى، لكنه عندما استيقظ
he witnessed a murder in the opposite ward and rushed to the scene!
!شاهد جريمةً في الجناح المقابل وهرع للمكان
But...
...لكن
Old man! Dr. Eto!
!عمّ! طبيب إيتو
Dr. Eto's murderer was you, Mori-kun!
!من قتل الطبيب إيتو كان أنت يا موري-كن
What?!
!مستحيل
No! The old man fell into a trap!
!كلا! وقع العمّ في فخّ
On the next Conan...
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Coffee.
قهوة
Next episode takes place at a scary hospital.
!مسرح الحلقة القادمة هو مشفى مخيف
I don't like needles!
!أنا أكره الحقن